ccn.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy – CCN.com

Effective date: October 24, 2018

[Hawkfish AS](https://www.hawkfish.com/) (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates [CCN.com](https://www.ccn.com/), also known as CCN.com, website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. Our Privacy Policy for Hawkfish AS is managed through [Free Privacy Policy](https://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/free-privacy-policy-generator.php).

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from CCN.com, Hacked.com, and MoneyMakers.com

## Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * Cookies and Usage Data

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  *  **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  *  **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  *  **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

## Use of Data

Hawkfish AS uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain the Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer care and support
  * To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
  * To monitor the usage of the Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To serve advertisements by e.g. Google Adsense and its partners.

## Advertisement partners that may collect data

Google https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/  
Aarki https://corp.aarki.com/privacy  
Adacado https://www.adacado.com/privacy-policy-april-25-2018/  
Adara Media https://adara.com/2018/04/10/adara-gdpr-faq/  
AdClear https://www.adclear.de/datenschutzerklaerung/  
ADEX https://theadex.com  
Adform https://site.adform.com/uncategorized/product-and-services-privacy-policy/  
Adikteev https://www.adikteev.com/eu/privacy/  
AdLedge https://adledge.com/data-privacy/  
Adloox https://adloox.com/disclaimer  
Adludio https://adludio.com/termsandconditions  
AdMaxim https://www.admaxim.com/admaxim-privacy-policy/  
Admedo https://www.admedo.com/privacy-policy  
Admetrics https://admetrics.io/en/privacy_policy/  
Adobe Advertising Cloud https://www.adobe.com/privacy/general-data-protection-regulation.html  
AdRoll, Inc. https://www.adroll.com/gdpr  
AdTriba https://privacy.adtriba.com/  
advanced STORE GmbH https://www.ad4mat.com/en/privacy/  
Adventori https://www.adventori.com/fr/avec-nous/mentions-legales/  
advolution.control https://advolution.de/privacy.php  
affilinet https://www.affili.net/uk/footeritem/privacy-policy  
Akamai https://www.akamai.com/compliance/privacy  
Amazon https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010  
Amobee https://www.amobee.com/trust/privacy-guidelines  
Analights https://analights.com/docs/analights-consent-to-the-processing-of-personal-data-en.pdf  
AppLovin Corp. https://www.applovin.com/privacy  
AppNexus https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy  
Arrivalist https://www.arrivalist.com/privacy#gdpr  
AudienceProject https://privacy.audienceproject.com/for-users/  
Aunica https://www.aunica.com.br/privacy/privacy.html  
Avocet https://avocet.io/privacy-portal  
Bannerflow https://www.bannerflow.com/privacy  
Batch Media https://batch.ba/datenschutzerklarung/  
BDSK Handels GmbH & Co. KG https://www.xxxlutz.de/ocms/privacy  
Beeswax https://www.beeswax.com/privacy.html  
Betgenius https://betting.geniussports.com/connextra-service-terms-conditions/  
Blismedia https://www.blis.com/privacy/  
Bombora https://bombora.com/privacy  
Booking.com https://www.booking.com/content/privacy.en-gb.html  
C3 Metrics https://c3metrics.com/privacy  
Cablato https://cablato.com/privacy  
Celtra https://www.celtra.com/privacy-policy/  
Centro https://www.centro.net/privacy-policy/  
Cint https://www.cint.com/participant-privacy-notice/  
Clinch https://clinch.co/pages/privacy.html  
Cloud Technologies https://green.erne.co/assets/PolicyCT.pdf  
Cloudflare https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/  
Commanders Act https://www.commandersact.com/en/privacy/  
comScore https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy  
Conversant/CJ Affiliate https://www.conversantmedia.eu/legal/privacy-policy  
Crimtan https://crimtan.com/privacy-ctl/  
Criteo https://www.criteo.com/privacy  
CUBED https://cubed.ai/privacy-policy/gdpr/  
DataXu https://www.dataxu.com/gdpr/  
Delta Projects https://www.deltaprojects.com/data-collection-policy/  
Demandbase https://www.demandbase.com/privacy-policy/  
DENTSU https://www.dentsu.co.jp/terms/data_policy.html  
Dentsu Aegis Network https://www.dentsu.com/termsofuse/data_policy.html  
Digiseg https://www.digiseg.io/GDPR/  
DMA Institute https://www.dma-institute.com/privacy-compliancy/  
DoubleVerify https://www.doubleverify.com/privacy/  
Dstillery https://dstillery.com/privacy-policy/  
DTS https://client.adhslx.com/privacy.html  
EASYmedia https://www.rvty.net/gdpr  
eBay https://www.ebay.com/help/policies/member-behaviour-policies/user-privacy-notice-privacy-policy?id=4260#section12  
ebuilders https://ebuilders.nl/privacy  
Effinity https://www.effiliation.com/politique-confidentialite.html  
emetriq https://www.emetriq.com/datenschutz/  
Ensighten https://www.ensighten.com/privacy-policy/  
Essens https://essens.no/privacy-policy/  
Evidon https://www.evidon.com/resources/privacy-statement/  
Exactag https://www.exactag.com/en/data-privacy  
Exponential https://exponential.com/privacy/  
Facebook https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update  
Flashtalking https://www.flashtalking.com/first-party-ad-serving/  
Fractional Media https://www.fractionalmedia.com/privacy-policy  
FUSIO BY S4M https://www.s4m.io/privacy-policy/  
Gemius https://www.gemius.com/cookie-policy.html  
GfK https://sensic.net/  
GP One https://www.gsi-one.org/templates/gsi/en/files/privacy_policy.pdf  
GroupM https://www.groupm.com/privacy-policy  
gskinner https://createjs.com/legal/privacy.html  
Haensel AMS https://haensel-ams.com/data-privacy/  
Havas Media France – DBi https://www.centraltag.com/commercial/policy/index.action  
hurra.com https://www.hurra.com/impressum  
IBM https://www.ibm.com/customer-engagement/digital-marketing/gdpr  
Ignition One https://www.ignitionone.com/privacy-policy/gdpr-subject-access-requests/  
Impact https://impact.com/privacy-policy/  
Index Exchange https://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/  
Infectious Media https://impressiondesk.com/  
Innovid https://www.innovid.com/privacy-policy  
Integral Ad Science https://www.integralads.com/privacy-policy  
intelliAd https://www.intelliad.de/datenschutz  
Interpublic Group https://www.interpublic.com/privacy-notice  
IPONWEB https://www.bidswitch.com/privacy-policy/  
Jivox https://www.jivox.com/privacy/  
Kantar https://www.kantarmedia.com/global/privacy-statement  
Kochava https://www.kochava.com/support-privacy/  
LifeStreet https://www.lifestreet.com/privacy  
Liftoff https://liftoff.io/privacy-policy/  
LiveRamp https://liveramp.com/service-privacy-policy/  
Localsensor https://www.localsensor.com/privacy.html  
LoopMe https://loopme.com/privacy/  
Lotame https://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/  
Macromill group https://www.metrixlab.com/privacy-statement/  
MainADV https://www.mainad.com/privacy-policy  
Manage.com https://www.manage.com/privacy-policy/  
Marketing Science Consulting Group, Inc. https://mktsci.com/privacy_policy.htm  
MBR Targeting Gmbh https://privacy.mbr-targeting.com  
MediaMath https://www.mediamath.com/privacy-policy/  
Meetrics https://www.meetrics.com/en/data-privacy/  
MindTake Research https://www.mindtake.com/en/reppublika-privacy-policy  
Mobitrans https://www.mobitrans.net/privacy-policy/  
Mobpro https://mobpro.com/privacy.html  
Moloco Ads https://www.molocoads.com/private-policy.html  
MSI-ACI https://site.msi-aci.com/Home/FlexTrackPrivacy  
Nano Interactive https://www.nanointeractive.com/privacy  
Navegg https://www.navegg.com/en/privacy-policy/  
Neodata Group https://www.neodatagroup.com/en/security-policy  
NEORY GmbH https://www.neory.com/privacy.html  
Netflix https://www.netflix.com/google-3PAS-info  
Netquest https://www.nicequest.com/us/privacy  
Neuralone https://web.neural.one/privacy-policy/  
Neustar https://www.home.neustar/privacy  
Nielsen https://www.nielsen.com/us/en/privacy-statement/digital-measurement.html  
numberly https://ads.1000mercis.com/us.html  
Oath https://policies.oath.com/xw/en/oath/privacy/enterprise/b2bprivacypolicy/  
Objective Partners https://www.objectivepartners.com/cookie-policy-and-privacy-statement/  
Omnicom Media Group https://www.omnicommediagroup.com/disclaimer.htm  
On Device Research https://ondeviceresearch.com/GDPR  
OneTag https://www.onetag.net/privacy/  
OpenX Technologies https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/  
Optomaton https://optomaton.com/privacy.html  
Oracle Data Cloud https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/marketing-cloud-data-cloud-privacy-policy.html  
OTTO https://www.otto.de/shoppages/service/datenschutz  
PERMODO https://permodo.com/de/privacy.html  
Pixalate https://www.pixalate.com/privacypolicy/  
Platform161 https://platform161.com/cookie-and-privacy-policy/  
PMG https://www.pmg.com/privacy-policy/  
Protected Media https://www.protected.media/privacy-policy/  
Publicis Media https://www.publicismedia.de/datenschutz/  
PubMatic https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/  
PulsePoint https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy  
Quantcast https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/  
Rackspace https://www.rackspace.com/gdpr  
Rakuten Marketing https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy  
Relay42 https://relay42.com/privacy  
Remerge https://remerge.io/privacy-policy.html  
Resonate https://www.resonate.com/privacy-policy/  
RevJet https://www.revjet.com/privacy  
RhythmOne LLC https://www.rhythmone.com/landing/gdpr  
RN SSI Group https://www.valuedopinions.co.uk/privacy  
Roq.ad https://www.roq.ad/privacy-policy  
RTB House https://www.rtbhouse.com/gdpr/  
Rubicon Project https://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-yield-optimization-privacy-policy/  
Salesforce DMP https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/  
Scenestealer https://www.scenestealer.tv/privacy-policy  
Scoota https://scoota.com/privacy-policy/  
Seenthis https://seenthis.co/privacy-notice-2018-04-18.pdf  
Semasio GmbH https://www.semasio.com/privacy-policy/  
SFR https://www.sfr.fr/securite-confidentialite.html  
Sift Media https://www.sift.co/privacy  
Simpli.fi https://www.simpli.fi/site-privacy-policy2/  
Sizmek https://www.sizmek.com/privacy-policy/  
Smaato https://www.smaato.com/privacy/  
Smadex https://smadex.com/end-user-privacy-policy/  
Smart https://smartadserver.com/company/privacy-policy/  
Smartology https://www.smartology.net/privacy-policy/  
Sociomantic https://www.sociomantic.com/privacy/en/  
Sojern https://www.sojern.com/privacy/product-privacy-policy/  
Sovrn https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/  
Spotad https://www.spotad.co/privacy-policy/  
SpotX https://www.spotx.tv/privacy-policy/  
TabMo https://static.tabmo.io.s3.amazonaws.com/privacy-policy/index.html  
Taboola https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy  
TACTIC™ Real-Time Marketing https://tacticrealtime.com/privacy/  
Teads https://teads.tv/privacy-policy/  
TEEMO https://teemo.co/fr/confidentialite/  
The Trade Desk https://www.thetradedesk.com/general/privacy-policy  
Tradedoubler AB https://www.tradedoubler.com/en/privacy-policy/  
travel audience – An Amadeus Company https://travelaudience.com/product-privacy-policy/  
TreSensa https://tresensa.com/eu-privacy/index.html  
TripleLift https://triplelift.com/privacy/  
TruEffect https://trueffect.com/privacy-policy/  
TrustArc https://www.trustarc.com/privacy-policy/  
Turbobytes https://www.turbobytes.com/gdpr/  
UDG https://www.udg.de/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/privacy_policy_EN.pdf  
usemax (Emego GmbH) https://www.usemax.de/?l=privacy  
Videology https://videologygroup.com/en/privacy-policy/  
Vimeo https://vimeo.com/cookie_policy  
Virtual Minds https://virtualminds.de/datenschutz/  
Vodafone GmbH https://www.vodafone.de/unternehmen/datenschutz-privatsphaere.html  
Waystack https://www.wayfair.com/customerservice/general_info.php#privacy  
Weborama https://weborama.com/e-privacy/  
White Ops https://www.whiteops.com/privacy  
Widespace https://www.widespace.com/legal/privacy-policy-notice/  
Wizaly https://www.wizaly.com/terms-of-use#privacy-policy  
Yieldr https://www.yieldr.com/privacy/  
ZMS https://zms.zalando.com/#  
Youtube https://www.youtube.com/  
Twitter https://twitter.com/  
Instagram https://www.instagram.com/  
Facebook https://www.facebook.com/

## Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Norway and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Norway and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Hawkfish AS will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure Of Data

### Legal Requirements

Hawkfish AS may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Hawkfish AS
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

## Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

  *  **Google Analytics** Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children’s Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email: jonas.borchgrevink@ccn.com
